Emergency Call: Level 1 Announcement
Omega 1 is rebooting.
Alpha 1 has begun reassembling its genomes.
It's been confirmed: exon replacement is occurring!
Nucleotide bases reaching 850 million...1.2 billion! It's way too fast!!
Confirmed: Alpha 1 has accessed the Raziel mainframe!
Fake-Net deployed! Alpha 1 evaded!
Activating emergency shields... We're locked out!
It's corrupting the entire matrix... Captain!?
Cut the cables manually!
Roger! Initiating cable explosives...
Ejection confirmed!
...No! No effect!
Omega 1 still progressing! It won't stop!
It's taken control of 98% of our weapons!
It's communicating with the Faust navigation system at an incredible speed.
Phase-space logic is being overridden!
Ergosphere is expanding,
and a plane is forming within the core!
We're switching to space warp mode!!
Alpha 1 is transmitting new coordinates to Faust!
The coordinates entered were NZ128, EZ061...
...Lost Jerusalem!!
So...it's going to invade like this...
Engine Room!
Insert the emergency break plug!!
...Engine Room?
Engin--
All civilians and crew members, evacuate now to the escape shuttles.
Launch in sequence following complete evacuation.
We hereby abandon this ship.
...All of you...leave now...
An evacuation order has been issued.
The ship will be abandoned.
All crew members, quickly proceed to shuttle boarding gates. Repeat--