Let's return to our world.
The way back...
is through that light.
It might be too late...
The dimensional shift has already begun.
Can you run?
Of course.
As long as you're by my side...
(Fei! Live!)
Ellyyyyy!
Karellen...
you...
There's not much time left.
The path is closing.
God is gone.
Now this world belongs to mankind.
You're free to walk your own path.
Karellen...you're not going back?
No...
I lost my humanity long ago.
I've committed too many sins to count.
I can't live as a human being anymore.
The only one who could have forgiven me...
...was God.
That's not true!
I'm sure everyone will understand!
There's plenty of time for you to atone! I believe in you, Karellen!
Still as kind as ever, Lacan.
I guess that's what it means to be human...
But I've already decided:
I will walk with God.
Besides, if I turned back now...
would there be a place for me...?
It is time.
Karellen...
I...
envy you two...